<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE MyCoReWebPage>
<MyCoReWebPage>
  <section xml:lang="all" title="Edition">
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-md-12">
        <h1>Edition</h1>
        <p>
          The CMO edition aims to provide, firstly, historically and textually accurate transcriptions of the
          available repertoire of Ottoman music as it was documented during the nineteenth century. These
          transcriptions, which reflect the original sources as closely as possible, will be made freely
          available to scholars as well as to musicians interested in historical performance practice.
          Secondly, the CMO project will publish critically edited texts from the corpus of Ottoman vocal
          music, following as faithfully as possible the original arrangement and orthography of the music
          manuscript sources, thus provide unique documentation of Ottoman poetry in its performative aspect.
        </p>
        <p>
          Musical transcriptions will be fully digitized, taking into account the special notational
          requirements of the musics of the Middle East and eastern Mediterranean. The data of both music
          and text editions will be stored in a variety of formats in order to provide access to the edition
          in both graphic (human readable) and semantic (machine readable) forms. Additionally, metadata for
          the manuscripts will be entered into the CMO source catalogue. Printed editions of single
          manuscripts will also be available as book-on-demand publications.
        </p>
        <p>
          Users can explore the edition according to the publication plan through the <u>browsing function</u>,
          or use the search field above to search for specific editions. The <u>guidelines</u> explain the
          methods of transcription and provide the necessary information to comprehend editorial decisions.
          See also the <u>list of abbreviations</u> for a better understanding of the transcriptions and critical
          commentaries. <u>User guide</u> gives detailed information on how to use the different functions on this
          web platform.
        </p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </section>
  <meta>
    <log date="2017-07-31" time="11:59" labelPath=" » About Edition" lastEditor="Kathleen Neumann" />
  </meta>
</MyCoReWebPage>