<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE MyCoReWebPage>
<MyCoReWebPage>
  <section xml:lang="all" title="Imprint">
    <h1>Imprint</h1>
    <h2>Legal note</h2>
    <p>
      Corpus Musicae Ottomanicae (CMO) is a joint project by the Institute for Musicology of
      Westfälischen Wilhelms-University Münster (WWU), WWU Institute for Arabic and Islamic
      Studies, Max Weber Foundation and Oriental Institute Istanbul, funded by the German
      Research Foundation (DFG).
    </p>
    
    <h2>Host</h2>
    <p>
      Max Weber Foundation <br />
      Max Weber Stiftung – Deutsche Geisteswissenschaftliche Institute im Ausland <br />
      Geschäftsstelle <br />
      Rheinallee 6 <br />
      53173 Bonn <br />
      Tel. +49-(0)228-37786-0 <br />
      Fax:+49-(0)228-37786-19 <br />
      Email: <span class="madress">info [at] maxweberstiftung.de</span>
    </p>
    <p>
      Max Weber Foundation is a federal, public law foundation with legal capacity based in
      Bonn and is represented by the Executive Director Dr. Harald Rosenbach.
    </p>
    
    <h2>Editor</h2>
    <p>
      Prof. Dr. Ralf Martin Jäger <br />
      Westfälische Wilhelms-Universität Münster <br />
      Fachbereich 8: Musikwissenschaft <br />
      Professur für Ethnomusikologie/Europäische Musikgeschichte <br />
      Philippistr. 2b <br />
      48149 Münster <br />
      Tel.: +49-(0)251-83-24444 <br />
      Fax: +49-(0)251-83-24450 <br />
      Email: <span class="madress">musik [at] uni-muenster.de</span>
    </p>

    <h2>Design and development</h2>
    <p>
      Head Office of the Union Library Network (GBV) <br />
      Platz der Göttinger Sieben 1 <br />
      37073 Göttingen <br />
      Germany <br />
      Tel.: +49(0)551/39-5207 <br />
      Fax: +49(0)551/39-13980 <br />
      Internet: <a href="http://www.gbv.de">http://www.gbv.de</a>
    </p>
    
    <h2>Disclaimer</h2>
    <p>
      We assume no guarantee for the timeliness, accuracy or completeness of the information
      displayed on this website. This also applies to all other websites to which reference
      is made by means of hyperlinks or URLs. WWU Institute for Musicology, WWU Institute for
      Arabic and Islamic Studies, Max Weber Foundation and the Oriental Institute are not
      responsible for their content, and we have neither selected nor altered the content of
      linked websites. The information on this website does not constitute legal or factual
      representations. CMO reserves the right to amend or supplement the information and data
      provided as required. CMO is not liable for any direct or indirect injury or damage
      arising from the use of the information or data contained on this website. There exist
      no rights or obligations between CMO and website users or third parties.
    </p>
    
    <h2>License</h2>
    <p>
      Unless otherwise stated, all content on www.corpus-musicae-ottomanicae.de is
      under Creative Commons ... 4.0 International License.
    </p>
    <p>
      The database is under Public Domain Dedication and License v1.0. 
    </p>
    <p>
      MyCoRe (used software) is available under GNU General Public License v3.0 . 
    </p>

  </section>
  <meta>
    <log date="2017-01-30" time="11:59" labelPath=" » Imprint" lastEditor="Kathleen Neumann" />
  </meta>
</MyCoReWebPage>
